<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><metadata>
    <idinfo>
        <citation>
            <citeinfo>
                <title>BIOSMap</title>
            </citeinfo>
        </citation>
        <descript>
            <abstract>The CalFish Abundance Database contains a comprehensive collection of anadromous fisheries abundance information. Beginning in 1998, the Pacific States Marine Fisheries Commission, the California Department of Fish and Game, and the National Marine Fisheries Service, began a cooperative project aimed at collecting, archiving, and entering into standardized electronic formats, the wealth of information generated by fisheries resource management agencies and tribes throughout California.Extensive data are currently available for chinook, coho, and steelhead. Major data categories include adult abundance population estimates, actual fish and/or carcass counts, counts of fish collected at dams, weirs, or traps, and redd counts. Harvest data has been compiled for many streams, and hatchery return data has been compiled for the states mitigation facilities. A draft format has been developed for juvenile abundance and awaits final approval. This CalFish Abundance Database shapefile was generated from fully routed 1:100,000 hydrography. In a few cases streams had to be added to the hydrography dataset in order to provide a means to create shapefiles to represent abundance data associated with them. Streams added were digitized at no more than 1:24,000 scale based on stream line images portrayed in 1:24,000 Digital Raster Graphics (DRG).These features generally represent abundance counts resulting from stream surveys. The linear features in this layer typically represent the location for which abundance data records apply. This would be the reach or length of stream surveyed, or the stream sections for which a given population estimate applies. In some cases the actual stream section surveyed was not specified and linear features represent the entire stream. In many cases there are multiple datasets associated with the same length of stream, and so, linear features overlap. Please view the associated datasets for detail regarding specific features. In CalFish these are accessed through the "link" that is visible when performing an identify or query operation. A URL string is provided with each feature in the downloadable data which can also be used to access the underlying datasets.The coho data that is available via the CalFish website is actually linked directly to the StreamNet website where the databases tabular data is currently stored. Additional information about StreamNet may be downloaded at http://www.streamnet.org. Complete documentation for the StreamNet database may be accessed at http://http://www.streamnet.org/def.html</abstract>
            <purpose>This coho shapefile is a component of the CalFish Abundance Database.  Linear and point features in the database depict the data collection sites associated with fisheries information that is currently contained in the CalFish Abundance Database.  This shapefile is not meant to reflect fish distribution</purpose>
        </descript>
        <keywords>
            <theme>
                <themekt>None</themekt>
                <themekey>Auth_CDFW</themekey>
                <themekey>California Department of Fish And Wildlife</themekey>
                <themekey>California Natural Resources Agency</themekey>
                <themekey>CAOpenData</themekey>
                <themekey>cn: silver salmon</themekey>
                <themekey>coho salmon</themekey>
                <themekey/>
                <themekey>sn: Oncorhynchus kisutch</themekey>
                <themekey>sample</themekey>
                <themekey>inventory</themekey>
                <themekey>monitoring</themekey>
                <themekey>fish</themekey>
                <themekey>reproduction</themekey>
                <themekey>abundance</themekey>
                <themekey>trend</themekey>
                <themekey>regulatory</themekey>
                <themekey>management</themekey>
                <themekey>planning</themekey>
                <themekey>special status species</themekey>
                <themekey>DS0183_20150325_wm</themekey>
            </theme>
        </keywords>
        <accconst>None</accconst>
        <useconst>License: This work is licensed under Creative Commons Attribution 4.0 International License (https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by/4.0/). Using the citation standards recommended for BIOS datasets (https://www.wildlife.ca.gov/Data/BIOS/Citing-BIOS) satisfies the attribution requirements of this license.Disclaimer: The State makes no claims, promises, or guarantees about the accuracy, completeness, reliability, or adequacy of these data and expressly disclaims liability for errors and omissions in these data. No warranty of any kind, implied, expressed, or statutory, including but not limited to the warranties of non-infringement of third party rights, title, merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose, and freedom from computer virus, is given with respect to these data.Data within the CalFish Anadromous Database was obtained from a variety of sources. Some count data may not be suitable for comparison or analysis. A short summary providing details of methodologies used to collect data and/or circumstances that may have affected the accuracy of the individual counts have been included in the dataset. The original reference material should be consulted when a more detailed description is appropriate.     Each data record within the database is associated with a reference. Copies of reference materials can be obtained from Connie Shannon at the CDFG Region 1, Cantara Office (530) 225-2155, or through the StreamNet Regional Library located in Portland,      http://www.fishlib.org</useconst>
        <datacred>Eric Haney; California Department of Fish and Wildlife (CDFW); (530) 225-2052; ; Eric.Haney@wildlife.ca.gov; </datacred>
    </idinfo>
    <metainfo>
        <metstdn>FGDC Content Standard for Digital Geospatial Metadata</metstdn>
        <metstdv>FGDC-STD-001-1998</metstdv>
        <mettc>local time</mettc>
    </metainfo>
</metadata>
